Today, I've got this proven six-step
process for building codec skills better
than 99% of people. So, let's not waste
any time and just get straight into this
one. All right, so these are the six
steps that I'm going to go over. I'm
going to explain each of these and tell
you why they're so important and then
we're going to get into Codex and
actually try some of the stuff out. And
real quick before we get started, I'm
going to talk about what actually is a
skill. So, if you already know what a
skill is, then just go ahead and skip
past this part. But for those of you who
need a refresher, here we go. So, I'm
going to use my chocolate chip pancake
analogy. Let's say we have this chef and
this chef makes the most amazing
chocolate chip pancakes and you want to
know how to make those. This is
essentially the output that you're
looking for. The way that you would be
able to copy this chef is by looking at
the recipe that the chef used or the
recipe that the chef made. So the chef
gives you the recipe. This is you. And
now you're able to pretty much make the
exact same output, the really, you know,
popular famous chocolate chip pancakes
because you followed the recipe. So this
recipe is basically the skill. This is
essentially the skill.mmd file which
means a markdown file. It's just a
simple language. It just means that
inside of the skill file there are like
pound signs and asterisks to indicate
like bullet points and headers and
things like that. So it's it's just
natural language. But then the agent is
basically able to take this skill file
and just use it so that if you say,
"Hey, Mr. AI agent, you know, make me
those chocolate chip pancakes." It
wouldn't have to be like, "Okay, well,
let me just do some research on how to
make them. And I don't know exactly what
kind of pancakes Nate wants. I don't
know how big they should be." So what
I'll do is I'll just follow this skill.
I'll follow the recipe and now I get the
same output that Nate's looking for and
I get it consistently the same every
single time because it's all documented
for me right here. And these can be
really simple. It can be a simple prompt
like, hey, you know, help me turn this
email into something that's more
professional or something that sounds
like me and maybe that's like my nate
email skill. But it could also be
complicated processes like doing
research on the market and analyzing,
you know, 50 stocks and telling you
which one to buy. So really, it's
whenever you want to basically like
codify some sort of process that you do
and so that you can delegate that
process to an agent and then you turn it
into a skill and now your agent can use
those skills. All right, so now that
that is out of the way, let's start with
number one up here where we have reverse
engineer. So the whole idea with reverse
engineering your skills is basically
that you want to start with an output.
You want to start with what is the
definition of done? What are you
actually looking for? Because let's say
you ask your agent here for chicken, for
example, and you actually want like
chicken parmesan on a bed of pasta, but
because you just said chicken, the agent
might interpret that a little bit
differently and make you a chicken
sandwich. And then next time you ask for
chicken, it might make you, you know,
chicken thighs. It doesn't actually know
specifically what you want. So if you
start with an output and you have, you
know, essentially this chicken parmesan
and you say, "Okay, let's reverse
engineer this food and see what went
into it, how long we cooked it, how did
we get here?" And that's how you build
the recipe. So, for example, if you
wanted to build a skill for the end of
the week report, you've got certain
columns in your Excel sheet. You've got
certain calculations that were made,
it's way easier to give the agent that
Excel sheet to give it the final
deliverable and say, "Hey, this is an
output that is really good and this is
what I want to build a skill for so that
you understand how to take some raw
input and turn it into this output that
I have already told you that I like and
this is what we're looking for every
time." And then it can basically walk
you backwards through that process.
Okay, what data did you look at? where
did you get it from? How did you
calculate it? Where did you format it?
You answer those questions and then you
have a version of a skill that already
knows sort of like the north star that
it's building towards. I think it's so
much easier to run the process, get the
output and say, "Okay, let's turn that
into a skill." Rather than saying, "Hey,
build me a skill for building a YouTube
dashboard." And then you might have this
vision and your agent might have a
completely different vision. And then
you're going to get frustrated when it
delivers you a chicken sandwich and you
actually wanted chicken parm. Now
remember, all of these concepts I'm
going to, you know, bring back together
when we actually hop into Codex and I
show you some stuff. But let's just keep
moving down the list because I think
this foundation is important. So number
two, we have one specific job and one
specific trigger. So remember how I said
that these skills are markdown files.
Skill.m MD. What happens in the skill.md
is you've got a YAML description. It's
called YAML front matter. And then
you've got the actual skill
instructions, which is the meat of the
skill. So right here is one of the
skills that I'm going to keep coming
back to in this video because it's it's
one of my favorite skills. And you can
see up here this metadata, this is the
YAML front matter. So if I view the
source, it looks like this. It's
actually just separated by these three
dashes. So this would be the YAML front
matter. And then everything below it
would be the actual instructions of the
skill. Now this is markdown. And when I
said markdown is very simple. It is. You
can see here are two pound signs. And
that just indicates a header. We can see
that we've got these little dashes which
are bullet points. And so when markdown
is actually rendered, it looks more
something like this. And you can see
it's just formatted better. So this is
the way that I like to look at it. But
if you click on view source inside of
the Codex app, you can see the raw
markdown file. But anyways, the metadata
up here is the YAML front matter and
that tells us what is the name of the
skill and when do you explicitly use it.
And there are other fields that can be
populated in here like in this one we
have an argument hint. And basically
this X article skill is used when I ask
my agent to turn an YouTube video into a
long form X post. And so sometimes it'll
feed in this argument which is my
YouTube video URL that it will take, it
will download, it will transcribe it, it
will take screenshots of it, all that
sort of, you know, all the stuff. And
then once the agent has basically said,
"Okay, cool. Nate wants to turn this
YouTube video into an X article." So,
okay, cool. I found this skill that I
need to use. Now that I know this is the
skill I'm going to invoke, let me read
the entire description of the skill. So
now I understand exactly what to
actually do. And you can see this skill
is pretty long. There's a lot of
instructions in here. And this wasn't
like me on one try turning this into a
skill. This is probably a skill that's
been iterated on 25 or more times. And
we'll talk more about that in a bit. But
the whole idea is that you want a skill
to do one very specific job. You don't
want to have a skill that's like run the
marketing team. You want to have a skill
that breaks that marketing team, all of
those processes into individual steps.
So in my book right up here, becoming AI
native, I talk about this and I call it
the function breakdown. I call it the
the tree. Basically, your job is a tree
and you've got different trunks with
different like, you know, bullet points
in your job description and then each of
those trunks have branches and each of
those branches have ultimately leaves
and you want to turn all of those little
leaves or those little tasks into skills
because you can chain skills together
over time. But the point being, if you
have a skill with one very specific job,
you can give it one very specific
trigger, which means that your agents
are going to be able to execute them
more consistently, invoke them
automatically. It just helps you
separate out what your agents are doing
in a much better way than if you have a
skill that's like 30 pages long and it's
supposed to do so many different things.
So think about breaking down processes
at the task level and turning each of
those tasks into skills. All right,
moving on to number three, we have
thinking about the freedom level. So
what I mean by this is when you're
automating things, you basically have to
figure out is this a deterministic
automation or a nondeterministic
automation? Basically, is this something
that's predictable and we know exactly
what comes in and we know exactly what
happens and we know exactly what comes
out or is it more of a non-deterministic
AI agent, more of a nondeterministic
black box where we know sort of what the
input's going to look like. We sort of
know what's going to happen inside the
process, but we do kind of know like
what the output should be. We still know
the definition of good and the
definition of done. You can think about
it like, can I automate this using
rules? Hard rules, hard logic. Is x
greater than 10? Is x equal to 500? or
is it something that needs a lot of
judgment? Analyze this. Turn this into
an email. Turn this into a spreadsheet.
And it's really important to think about
where does your skill live on that
spectrum? Because if you have a very
deterministic skill, like for example,
it just has to take a Excel sheet and it
just has to populate the cells into the
CRM or something and that's basically
just data processing transferring.
That's a very deterministic process. And
if you write the skill in a very
non-deterministic way, there's a lot
more room for error. There's a lot more
room for AI to interpret something wrong
and do something wrong. And that's the
case where you want the skill to be like
step one do this, step two, do this.
Exactly. Exactly. Exactly. Do this. It's
very specific. But if you've got
something nondeterministic, like for
example, my ex article skill, we don't
want to be so specific. We want the AI
to be able to use its judgment and to be
able to use research and thinking to
generate a unique output because every
YouTube video is different, which means
every X article is going to be
different, which means all the
screenshots that it needs to take are
going to be different. I couldn't say
something like screenshot the video at
the 1 minute mark and then the
two-minute mark and then the 5minute
mark and put those into the article at
line 400, line 600, line 700 because
then the articles would come out feeling
generic and they probably wouldn't even
make sense and it just wouldn't be a
very good output. So think about the
freedom level of the process and when
you're doing this manually, do you
follow the same set of instructions
every time or are you constantly using
judgment and are you constantly doing
different things within the process to
ultimately get to that definition of
good? By the way, guys, I've got this
completely free SOP for you about
getting your first Amation client. It's
going to go over the exact steps that
has been proven for hundreds of our AIS
Plus members to get their first paid
gigs. It goes over the one-s sentence
service pitch that can get you started
today, why your first client should cost
you money, the 5-minute video that
answers, can this person actually
deliver before you've actually received
any money, what to do when you have zero
case studies. There's so many good
things in here that are going to help
you out. Even if you already do have
clients, I would recommend grabbing this
because, like I said, it's yours
completely free. So, if you want to grab
this, there's a link for it down in the
description. Let's get back to the
video. All right, moving on to number
four. We have verification. And this is
probably the most important piece of
building skills. So, the whole idea of
building a skill is that now you can
trust that your agent's going to give
you an output more consistently that
meets your standard. But what you want
to do in there is you don't want to be
constantly being handed the agents V1.
you want to be handed an output that's
already good to go that you can give it
a quick skim, approve it all and then
shoot it off. And the cool thing about
agents building stuff to ultimately
achieve some sort of northstar is that
you can also have agents check its own
work, verify its own work or you know
other agents verify different agents
work. So every single skill that I build
works in some sort of verification loop
meaning the agent who builds the thing
delivers this output and then we either
have the same agent or different sub
agents come in and verify that output
and then provide feedback. And this
verification loop can go on multiple
times. Sometimes it's just, hey, here's
the V2 and it's approved. Here's the V7.
I've even had agents verify over and
over and give me like a V15 or 16. And
that basically just ensures that your
time isn't being wasted verifying and
sending feedback when you can have
agents do that for you. Now, when it
comes to verification, there is a
difference between objective checks and
subjective checks. So, let me explain
what I mean by that. An objective check
is something that can literally be
proven. Sort of like the
nondeterministic versus deterministic
thing. Objective means okay um I wanted
you to do research and then the
verification was to pull in 500 sources
cut that down to the best 250 and then
every single fact that's in the article
I want that to be double checked by
second agent and that's objective we can
literally prove 500 sources cut down to
250 every single fact double checked by
a different agent that's objective that
is a rule does x equal y is a greater
than b but then you have some things
that are subjective like verifying the
video right if it's it's creating a
video for you or if it's creating a
website for you. A lot of these
subjective checks are more like, oh, you
know, does everything look good? Is
everything inbounds? Is it loading in a
certain way? When you don't have an
actual hard metric to align it to, you
have to sort of be a little bit more
subjective on your verification. And
what you're thinking about doing is
turning that agent into an LLM as a
judge, which basically means, okay, so
if AI is going to be applying its
approval, and it has to use judgment to
approve, then how can you tell the agent
exactly what you're looking for? What
does good typically look like or feel
like even though there's not a hard
rule? So, for example, with the X
article skill, I've got some objective
checks in there like there are 10
screenshots from the video. But then
there's other subjective checks like how
do you make it flow in a way that makes
sense? How do you make it sound like
Nate? How do you make sure that the
images that are put into the the
article, the screenshots are cropped?
There's other subjective checks that we
have to let it do things where it like
opens up the app and it scrolls through
and it reads through and it screenshots
and it verifies. But a lot of those
checks, like I said, are more
subjective. And so that's where
iterating on these skills takes a lot of
time because you're constantly running
the skill, analyzing the output, giving
feedback, running the skill again,
analyzing the output, giving feedback,
and you're basically just like training
the skill where every single time you
use it, it gets better. But the thing
about verification is there's always a
way. You might be thinking to yourself,
well, I don't really know how I would
have agents verify that process. Agents
can do anything. They can use your
computer. They can use your browser.
They can look at things. They can listen
to things. They can do anything. So just
think about it like this. If you
assigned that task to a human, what
would you do to basically give it the
stamp of approval? And then just explain
that to the agent and that's your
verification. That doesn't mean it's
going to always come out 100%, but it's
going to be more like 95% rather than
giving you something that started off at
like 75 or 80. Okay. And moving on to
number five, we've got walk it down. And
when I say walk it down, I mean walking
it down the model list. So whether
you're using cloud code or codeex, we
all know that different models have
different strengths. And we all know
that models that have the strongest
strengths are the most expensive. So for
example, Astra is more expensive than
Soul, but more capable than Soul. Soul
is more expensive than Terra, but more
capable than Terra. So the idea is you
build a skill and you're getting this
good output. And maybe you were testing
that with Astra. Okay. Well, let's run
that same skill on Soul. Are we getting
the same result? If we're getting the
same result and it's cheaper, okay,
let's test it on Terra now. Are we
getting the same result? Is it cheaper?
Okay, let's test it on Luna. There's no
reason to be running a skill with Astra
if you could run it with Luna and get
the exact same output. But it is
important to test it because not every
skill fits that. I've had some skills
where I run them on Haiku or Luna
because they're just super simple. For
example, when I give my agent a YouTube
video and I say, "Hey, I need a YouTube
video description and timestamps. That I
can do with Luna, and doing it with
Astra is overkill. But for this X
article thing, I typically like to use
at least Soul or Astra because it just
has a better understanding of
screenshotting things and putting it in
the right spot and cropping it down and
even blurring things out. It's so much
better with the browser use with Soul
and Astra. And then once you've landed
on a model that you like, you can take
that one step further and you can walk
it down the effort level. So start it
off on maybe high and if it's not good
enough, then move it up a little bit.
And if it is good, then move it down to
medium and just keep finding basically
the simplest model or the lightest and
cheapest model that still executes at
the level of quality that you're looking
for. And then moving on here to number
six, we have the bike method, which is
I've kind of already alluded it to it
multiple times throughout this video so
far, but really it's just the idea to me
that your skill is never done. Every
single time you run the skill, you're
going to improve it. You're going to
say, "Hey, here's what I really liked.
Here's what I didn't like. Update the
skill so that next time it's better."
Almost every single time I run a skill,
I give it feedback and I tell it to
update. And if you think about this,
like you're teaching a kid to ride a
bike, that's what a skill really should
feel like. You start off very cautious.
You're watching everything. You're
guiding them. You you've got your hand
on the the the steering wheel. Steering
wheel, I meant like handlebars. And
you're you're right there. And then what
happens is you give feedback. You say
like, "Okay, that was good, but you
know, you were leaning a bit too far to
the left. Make sure your weight's more
in the center." And then you keep going.
Eventually, you take off the training
wheels because the skill is getting
better and you're getting more trust in
the skill. and then you give more
feedback again and then eventually you
take off the elbow pads, right? And then
you keep giving feedback. But that
doesn't mean that you just take off the
kid's helmet and let them bike on the
highway. You're not going to do
something reckless like that. You're
also not just going to shoot them off
down the road and then go inside and
take a nap. You're still going to be in
in some way watching or having certain
guardrails in place in order to make you
feel comfortable and in order for you to
have more trust in the actual skill
itself. And I truly believe in the idea
that there's no such thing as a finished
product unless your skill is super super
deterministic and it runs perfect every
time and you don't have to worry about
it. But when the skills are more on the
judgment side of the spectrum, you know,
as we talked about up here, the more
your skills live over here, the less I
believe that you can actually have a
finished skill because like I said,
every time things might happen a little
bit differently and every time your
process might change or new models might
drop and you're just constantly going to
be giving feedback every time you use
it. Okay, so let's hop into Codeex here
and we can take a look at how this
actually works. Now when you are inside
of your project and if you're inside of
your AIOS which is usually what I'm
building in the codec skills will live
in a folder called the aagents and then
inside of the aagents there's a skill or
sorry not a skill there's another folder
calledkills and if you're doing this in
cloud code the skills live in aclad and
then in a folder called skills now these
can be transferable I basically just
tell codeex or claude hey see all the
skills in there and bring them over here
too so just I have duplicates of them
but that's where they actually live
inside of your um project unless you
have them at a global level which just
means they're living locally across all
of your Codex projects rather than just
inside of your AOS. So that's where they
live and you can always just say, "Hey,
you know, Codex, I have this skill. I
don't remember where it is. Could you
show me the file path?" And it will find
it and you can move it if you want. But
anyways, that's where they live. And you
can see I actually just ran this ex
article skill on a video. So it says,
"Your ex article draft is saved." I'll
click into it. And I actually did
obviously already publish this one, but
I didn't even have to change anything. I
basically just clicked in here. I read
it all and I published it. And you can
see that as it's going through, it
already formatted everything and it used
the video. Of course, it took
screenshots of things and it like put
them in the right spot to line up with
what was actually being said in the
article. And it even added this little
um I don't know what you want to call
it, like a spotlight. It added that. I
didn't actually do that, but it will
basically crop things out and it will
add things like that into my actual
article because I've told it in the
skill to do things like that. And you
can see that for this specific video,
this ran on GBD6 Astra. So, what I'm
going to do real quick is I'm going to
walk this down. I'm going to give this
same prompt to Soul and Terra and tell
it to make the X article and it's going
to use the skill. And we'll see how
those outputs compare to Astra's output
because this is a pretty complex skill.
It has to transcribe the video. It has
to open up the article. It has to make
the thumbnail. It has to format
everything and it has to screenshot
everything and put it in and then
actually like drag it around. So there's
a lot of browser use and there is a ton
of judgment inside of this. Like I said,
this is not a deterministic skill. So
you can see right now I have Soul,
Terra, and Luna all running. It's been
about 10 minutes, so I'll just check
with you guys when this is done. But I
just wanted to show you how all of them
because of the skill, because of the
verification, are viewing images. You
can see how many times Luna has viewed
these images here because it's taking
screenshots and it's trying to
understand, okay, which of these should
be worked into the article and where and
why. Same thing down here with Soul.
Obviously, this one is a super super
visualheavy sort of skill, but because
I've worked that in there, all of them
are viewing images no matter what. And
so, it'll be really interesting to see
how they decide to place them and, you
know, what images they actually choose
to put in there because X limits you to
a certain amount of images per article.
So, I'm going to let these run. We'll
compare the results and we'll kind of
talk about how walking it down has
changed my perspective on this specific
skill. All right, so you can see now
that we have Luna and Terra have
finished up. Soul is still working. So,
we'll start reviewing these two and then
we'll hop over to Soul. Hopefully, it'll
be done by the time we're looking
through these. So, Luna took 28 minutes
and 33 seconds. Let's open up the draft
and see what we are working with. So, we
have um the thumbnail in there. We have
I designed a one person million-dollar
business with Claude. Um the title is
the same as like the opening line, which
I don't love. There's also this weird
spacing was right there. I don't know if
it tried to like center it, but I do
notice that. Anyways, we have sort of
like the TLDDR. We have these different
headers here. I'm yet to see an image.
Here comes the first screenshot. So,
this is talking about um the three
different types of ideas to compare. And
in the screenshot, we do see all three.
So, that matches up pretty well. Um we
see agent report card as well as down
here. So, really what I'm checking for
right now is that it all sounds like me.
So, this is kind of trained on like my
LinkedIn style guide and my YouTube
style guide and like the way that I
speak, but I'm also making sure that the
images look good. So, the test suite is
a golden data set. We know what the
correct answer or correct action should
be. And we see an evaluation right here.
The first run scored 88. That's what we
see. Um, approved the new policy. Same
16 tests. Ran it again. That looks
decent. I clicked create report and we
don't really see the report here. So,
that's a little bit off, I would say,
but it's not too bad. I'm actually
impressed that Luna is doing it this
well. This is customer support. This is
kind of just the home dashboard. And
then down here we see searching for
companies using clay. It did do a nice
little spotlight animation here when
we're looking at the actual pricing. And
then we've got the three Ps down here.
Okay. So, this is not too bad. We'll
have to compare, but I would say that I
was impressed by Luna's ability to
screenshot, add spotlights, put it in
the right spots. So, that is Luna. That
also took 28 minutes and 30 seconds.
Okay. So, we have Terara. And by the
way, all of these are running on high.
So, we have Terara here. Took 26
minutes. So, about 2 minutes, 2 and a
half minutes faster than Luna. Let's
open up this draft. See what we got. So,
same exact um thumbnail. We have an
image right away. How I built a $1
million AI business model with Claude.
This image isn't great. Like to start
off the article like that. That's not a
very strong way to start it off because
it looks like it's cut off like that.
So, that's bad. Um we go through the
three filters.
Oof. I mean, [snorts] this image doesn't
look very good either. I would already
say right now that um Luna did a better
job. I mean, this isn't a bad Also, this
is a zoomed in. So, it took a screenshot
of the video and then it zoomed in on
the score going from 88 to 94. So,
that's not terrible. Read complaint
check company fit recommend small trial.
What you'll notice here is it actually,
if I can open this up, it redacted
sensitive details. So, it put this block
over it and said sensitive details
redacted. So, I think that that's pretty
cool. I like when it does things like
that. It did a little spotlight effect
here. It redacted more sensitive details
in this one. As you can see, it did it
again here. So, it's it did it again
here. It It shows so many times when it
needed to redact sensitive details. It
did it again. It did it again. Okay, but
this is obviously an issue. It didn't
verify this good enough. Like, you can
see that there's literally four images
in a row down here. This one looks bad.
I think that, you know, you you you have
to use the browser to like drag these
around. And I think that it just gave up
or it stopped and thought it was done.
So, so far I would say that Luna did a
better job than Terra. And Terra was,
you know, it's a more capable model
apparently than Luna. It's also more
expensive. So, right now, if I was
choosing between these, I would choose
Luna. But now Soul just finished up and
Soul took 38 minutes. So, normally when
I do run this, I run this on Astra. I
usually run this on Astra low and I run
it on fast mode to get it done faster.
But let's see. This did it. Let me open
this up. Okay, so here is uh Soul's
version. I built a $1 million business
with Claude. We have the same sort of
like TLDDR, the three filters. We have a
picture of the three filters right here.
So, that's not bad. Choosing the
product. Okay, it's zoomed in here.
These are all zoomed in, by the way. So,
it's it's it's using more, I guess,
vision intelligence to choose what to
actually display in the image. You can
see it redacted here the demo receipt.
So, not too bad. It zoomed in a little
bit here on the report, although we
don't see the score 88. What it what it
highlighted here was 14 tests pass and
two failed instead of showing us the 88.
So, just pointing that out. It also
zoomed in down here on some analysis of
that report. It did a little spotlight
effect here to show the 94. It redacted
more of these receipts. It did another
spotlight here. It shows sales and
support without losing control. So,
that's not terrible. We've got this
customer support image as well. We've
got more internal source ID redacted.
Another spotlight effect on the money.
And yeah, so this one isn't too bad
either. I would say honestly like I'm
wondering if Luna's was better. And
that's the thing, like these are so
different and sometimes I have tutorial
videos, sometimes I have more of this
style where they're edited. So, it's
very hard to just say, "Okay, I've run
one test and I know that now I'm going
to go with Luna instead of like Astra or
something for for a specific example."
Now, I will tell you guys, I've done
this multiple times on multiple
different YouTube videos and Astra just
seems to be the best. So, I do stick
with Astra on low, but I do think it's
worth running them through a few
different examples and and
understanding. And that's why I said
that there's really no such thing as a
finished product, especially the more
non-deterministic you get on that whole
spectrum. And what you can see about all
of these with Luna, it gave us a QA
report, it gave us a visual plan, and it
gave us selected frames. Terra gave us a
QA report as well. And Soul gave us a QA
report. And like I said, that's the most
important part is just them proving that
they've verified stuff. So, it verified
the title, the body, 76 non-mpt text
blocks, um 11 inline screenshots, seven
H2 headings, visual review and privacy,
editorial coverage, artifacts. It's
proving to me that it's done. And it's
proving to me that it did its
verification. And trust me, if it didn't
do this QA report and it didn't do the
verification, this skill would be so
much worse as far as actually getting it
to place the screenshots in the right
spot. So, for this specific example of
the skill, let me talk about how I did
all of these things. I took an article
that I did manually and I did a few of
these manually where I literally went
through the YouTube video, screenshotted
things, put it in the right spot and I
gave it some of those to look at. So,
first was like, hey, analyze all these
outputs. I want to turn this into a
skill. So, help me understand like
what's good about these and and how do
you choose the screenshots and how do
you place them and things like that. So,
I reverse engineered and then obviously
this is one very specific job. It was to
turn a YouTube video into an X article.
It's not just to write X articles in
general. We've got I've got a different
skill for that. This is literally to
turn a YouTube video into an X article,
which means the trigger is very specific
as well. So here, all I said was turn
this YouTube video into an X article and
it automatically was able to invoke the
X article skill as you can see. But if I
wanted to do a slash command and do X
article, I can invoke the skill like
that as well. But typically, if I say,
hey, I want this YouTube video to be
turned into an X article, it just
invokes the skill automatically because
it's one specific use case and it's one
specific trigger. We talked about the
freedom level in here a lot. This is
obviously a super super non-eterministic
process. We talked about the
verification. We did the walking it down
live. And as far as the bike method,
like I said, guys, I would basically
come into here and I would look at what
Tara did that I didn't like. And I would
basically be like, "Okay, Tara, so in
your article, you had some really weird
screenshots in the beginning. It looked
like things were cropped out." The whole
idea is that people can look at the
screenshot and they won't need context
of what happened a few seconds before
that frame or a few seconds after. And
you have multiple examples in here like
the first screenshot you did as well as
the second screenshot that you did that
just don't look very good. You also have
things at the end like these random four
images that don't feel like they're
placed right. So I feel like your
verification wasn't good enough, but
also the third the third image in this
set of or sorry the second image in this
set of three at the bottom it's like
halfway through an animation. So that
was first of all a bad screenshot to
take and second of all a bad place to
put it. So that's some of the feedback
that I have for you now. If you could
analyze this, understand what I mean by
this and then update the skill so that
you don't make these mistakes in the
future and so that you can highlight
some of the important things that I just
mentioned blah blah blah. And then I
would just shoot that off and it would
go through, it would look at the
feedback and it would take all of that
information and it would update the
skill. And that is how you start to sort
of see that bike method coming into play
every single run, give good feedback and
also give bad feedback and tell it to
update the skill. Otherwise, all of
those changes that you have to make
manually, you're going to have to make
manually again the next time. So anyways
guys, those were the six tips. Those
were all of them ran on a real example
of one of the skills that I use pretty
much every day. Every time I make a
YouTube video. So I appreciate you guys
watching through all that. And also
guys, real quick, just wanted to tell
you about my second channel where I just
kind of like document these things that
I'm doing at AI events or these
different trips I'm taking to meet up
with AI creators or speaking at things.
And if you want to check out sort of
like what else I'm into besides just
like making tutorials, then head over to
the second channel. I'll put the link in
the description. And I hope to see you
guys over there. I hope you enjoy this
type of content as well. But that's
going to do it for today. So if you guys
enjoyed the video or you learned
something new, please give it a like. It
helps me out a ton. And as always, I
appreciate you guys making it to the end
of the video. And I'll see you on the
next one. Thanks everyone.